[
    {
        "front": "まえ",
        "back": "前 \nThe front",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みっかまえ",
        "back": "三日前 \nThree days ago",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜんはん",
        "back": "前半 \nThe first half",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "あと",
        "back": "あと \nAfter, later",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "うしろ",
        "back": "後ろ \nBack, behind",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "そと",
        "back": "外 \nBack and forth",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "がいこく",
        "back": "外国 \nForeigh country",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひだり",
        "back": "左 \nLeft",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひだりて",
        "back": "左手 \nLefthand",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みぎ",
        "back": "右 \nRight",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みぎて",
        "back": "右手 \nRighthand",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひがし",
        "back": "東 \nEast",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひがしぐち",
        "back": "東口 \nThe east gate",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "にち",
        "back": "西 \nWest",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "にちぐち",
        "back": "西口 \nThe west gate",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みなみ",
        "back": "南 \nSouth",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みなみぐち",
        "back": "南口 \nThe south gate",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "きた",
        "back": "北 \nNorth",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "きたぐち",
        "back": "北口 \nThe north gate",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "なまえ",
        "back": "名前 \nName",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうめい",
        "back": "十名 \n10 people",
        "chapter": "N5 K6"
    }
]